CV · Britta Eggert - 1 -

Myrtenweg 22 33699 Bielefeld

Mobile: 0049 176 601 433 76

Email: britta@familyeggert.com

PERSONAL SKILLS

Reliability Team spirit Creative thinking

SOFTWARE SKILLS

InDesign Photoshop Illustrator

PERSONAL SUMMARY

A highly structured yet flexible graphic designer. Delivers creative and innovative solutions – from inception through production to final delivery, ensuring that all work is completed and delivered within agreed timetables. Able to work as part of a team with printers, copywriters, photographers, other designers, web developers and marketing specialists.

KEY SKILLS AND COMPETENCIES

Self-employed since November 2004.

Successfully worked for 5 years as graphic designer in Bielefeld, Germany. In 2009, joined partner and programmer in the successful development and administration of the design and development firm, forty degrees, in Sweden.

Responsible for print design as well as web design for forty degrees. Creates graphic design solutions from concept through final delivery. Consuls customers and networks with involved companies and various service providers to get best results.

Experienced in graphics design, concept design, logo development, designing business documents, folder and brochure layouts, promotional materials and campaigns, corporate design, packaging design, image editing, photo retouching, web design, printing preparation, research, consulting and general services.

LANGUAGES

German, native, spoken and written. English, fluent, spoken and written. Swedish, good.

PERSONAL SITUATION

Married, two children.

PERSONAL INTERESTS

Family, sport, cooking.

CV · Britta Eggert - 2 -

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS

1985 - 1991

Secondary school exams with High School-Entrance Diploma Realschule Heepen, Bielefeld, Germany

1992 - 1994

Education to professional preschool teacher Carl-Severing Schule, Bielefeld, Germany

2001 - 2003

Retraining to media designer for digital and print media Symmedia Akademie, Bielefeld, Germany

Final examination of IHK Hannover

WORK EXPERIENCES

1995 - 1996

Kindergarten teacher Kindergarten "Christophorus" Bielefeld, Germany

1996 - 1997

Kindergarten teacher and group leader Day care center "Ramba Zamba", Bielefeld, Germany

1997 - 2001

Nurse for a family with 4 children Fredebeul, Bielefeld, Germany

2004 - 2013

Self-employed as graphic designer

2009 - 2013

Graphic designer in own company 'forty degrees' Print & Web Agency with international customers

2013 - 2022

Self-employed as graphic designer, half time